Welcome to Team WOW.
First off, congratulations and welcome to the team.
My name is Coach Bobby, and I'm one of the team leads here at Team
WOW. Over the next three days, we're going to give you the
tools, knowledge, and confidence you need to be successful
in your new role.
Now, before we jump into training, I want you to know something
important. You're not just joining a pizza company.
You're joining a team that believes in growth, opportunity, and creating
the best customer experience possible.
At Team WOW, our mission is simple.
We're dedicated to delivering the best customer experience possible.
Everything we do, from answering the phone, to making pizzas, to
even delivering orders, starts with that mission.
Now, to help prepare you for that mission, I've assembled an elite team.
That team is composed of some new and some seasoned pizza athletes,
who are all fanatic about development and making sure you are made for more.
Our team. Hey, how's it going, guys?
My name is Bobby. I am with Team WOW in the Dallas market.
I've been with Domino's for about 13 years.
I began as a CSR, and I am currently a DO and team
coach for all of Team WOW.
Hi, my name is Stephanie Castaneda.
I started as a CSR 16 years ago, and I'm currently a director of
operations for the Dallas market.
Hi, my name is Claudia Diaz. I started with Domino's in 1991 as a delivery
driver at the store on Delta. Currently, I'm the director of operations for
Team WOW in El Paso.
Hi, my name is Juan Olivares. I started with Domino's Pizza in
1987 as a delivery expert. Three
months into that position, I was offered to be an assistant manager,
and eventually, I became a manager.
And the first store that I managed was in San Antonio, Texas.
Currently, I'm the training director here for Team WOW in El Paso, Texas.
Hi, my name is Victor Barajas. I'm with Team WOW in the Los Angeles market.
I began my Domino's journey in 2017, nine years ago,
as a customer service representative.
Now, I'm the director of operations, and I look forward to welcoming you to
Team WOW.
Hi, this is Richard Kesky, and I'm with Team WOW here in
the Denver market. I began my Domino's journey in
1995, 31 years ago, as a pizza
maker and CSR, and today, I'm the HR
director for all of Team WOW. Welcome.
Over the next three days, you'll learn the fundamentals that make our stores
successful. We'll focus on four key areas:
service,
uniform and professionalism,
safety and workplace standards,
and execution.
You'll complete online training modules, participate in hands-on experiences with
your trainer, and spend time learning how our stores operate day to day.
Don't worry if you don't know everything yet, that's exactly why we're here.
Ask questions, get involved, be curious.
The more effort you'll put into the next three days, the more you'll get out of
them.
And remember, nobody expects perfection on day one.
What we do expect is a great attitude and a willingness to
learn and a commitment to improving every day.
We're excited to have you here, and we're looking forward to seeing what you'll
accomplish as a part of Team WOW.
Let's get started, and welcome to the team